DANI HARTLEY

7620 Nunsland Dr., Austin, TX 78744 · 801-349-8311 dani_hartley@msn.com

Highly innovated and efficient Operations Manager specializing in distribution and logistics. Offering an array of critical skills in labor management, productivity, quality assurance, leadership, facility management and accurate data tracking. Proven history of increasing productivity with employee morale-boosting initiatives.

EXPERIENCE

06/2016-03/2021

OPERATIONS MANAGER I-III, AMAZON

Operations Manager III

- Mentoring, training and developing team members for career progression, performance improvement and recognition purposes
- Set the vision, direction and culture of the team by managing individual and team performance expectations and goals, monitoring real time service levels and schedule adherence, and holding the team accountable to meet and exceed performance targets
- Achieve site-wide improvements in Operations, Quality, Productivity, Cost, Customer experience and People metrics.
- Build partnerships with internal and external teams to collaborate and drive measurable improvements in areas that cause impact both the upstream and downstream partners and customer service.
- Cultivated a culture of inclusion and diversity by re-establishing and launching new Affinity Groups and Committee program, providing oversight and guidance to the owners of 7 total organizations. Developed a structured system to ensure that the planning meetings and events serviced the associates, gave back to the community, and coincided with building needs.
- As the SME (Subject Matter Expert) for ADAPT, completed a rate validation on sites ADAPT (Associate Development and Performance Tracking) program to ensure that the proper thresholds were set in each process path. Ultimately level set 13 rate that were out of tolerance resulting in average of a 57 uph increase across each path.
- ADAPT SME for SAT2 completing quarterly building-wide rate validation for all direct paths and rolling out necessary communication plans.

Operations Manager II

- Site Lead 1 Ops Manager, 6 Area Managers, 8 Shift Assistants, 300 warehouse associates.
- Implemented a 30 day onboarding program for new associates, welcoming them to Amazon with additional classroom trainings and hands-on up and downstream experience, reducing new hire attrition by 4%.
- Implemented a real time add back program for amnesty reducing cost per amnesty from \$5.72 to \$5.03 along with a 48% reduction in overall SRC spend.

Operations Manager I

- Ensured all associates had the necessary training, knowledge and tools to be successful.
- Monitored employee productivity and optimized procedures to reduce costs.
- Responsible for communicating policies to Associates and acting as the primary information source for the team.
- Supported and upheld compliance to all safety programs to ensure a safe work environment.
- Oversaw development and launch of the problem solve process correcting defects, accessing product status.
- Founded and launched the Sister AM program, increasing operational flexibility building-wide by focusing on cross-training interdepartmentally, as opposed to confining associates to intra-department mobility.

- Trained 5 new Area Managers on both soft and hard skills such as technical knowledge of the RSP, strategic planning and staffing, and associate engagement.
- Created and implemented an AM Deep Dive Board that required leadership to spend 1 hour in path weekly to better identify pain points in the process, waste, and any gaps with training.

Created and developed a problem solve program for SAT2's launch, used to onboard/train over 40 new problem solvers.

08/2015-06/2016

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANAT, UNIVERSITY OF UTAH

- Reviewed applications Data entry
- Creation of program documents
- Event Planning and Coordination
- -Management of Office supplies

08/2012-02/2015

LEAD TELLER, AMERICA FIRST CREDIT UNION

- Oversees the staffing, coaching, and performance management of all tellers
- -Coordinates workflow and day-to-day operations of all Tellers
- Assists Tellers with identifying and correcting out-of-balance conditions
- Ensures that Tellers adhere to all current policies, procedures and regulations including compliance and security
- Balances out branch to standard cash limit, prepares cash shipments to Federal Reserve intermediary banking institution and reconciles cash general ledger account
- Maintains and controls vault cash

EDUCATION

03/2020-CURRENT

CODING BOOTCAMP, UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS

05/2013-05/2016

B.S. IN OPERATIONS MANAGEMENT, UNIVERSITY OF UTAH

05/2013-05/2016

B.A. IN INTERNATIONAL STUDIES, UNIVERSITY OF UTAH